Seino, Galgal Channel, Go Go!
Let's go, Galgal Channel, go, go, go!
Yes, that's right, today we're going to have a championship. Today, we're going to have a championship.
Explanation?
Well, we want to see how well you can do the lines and other important parts of our songs.
Can we do it with sirens?
It's not a corner, it's a project.
Yes!
Start the video!
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Okay, first one.
The first song is by Claire from Eighty's Lover, before she goes like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
She is going to do this part by herself and come forward.
Yes.
Who will play first?
I'm not sure about this one.
But you did change positions, didn't you?
That's right.
It's so messed up.
It's like, what's this?
Okay, I'll go first.
Well, I'll go first.
Please do your best.
Oh no.
It's difficult.
Well then.
Pan.
Pang.
Timing is difficult.
Is this right?
It fits.
I don't know if it's right or not.
Then let's do it again in a row.
Ah...
Let's do it.Let's do it, let's do it.
Let's split it up.
Sure, let's do that.
Let's do that.
Yes, sir.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Pan, pan, pan, pan, pan, pan.
Sure, there's a pause anything in there.
Okay, here we go.
Pan, pon, se-no. Pan, pan, pan, pan, pan.
I don't know, maybe it's a pose.
Okay, one more time.
Woof, woof, woof, woof, woof.
Pan, pan, pan, pan, pan, pan.
Crackle.
Hey, this one's funny, like a daytime character.
It's hard when it's "okey-dokey." That's for sure.
Crazy girl's going to lunch.
That's right.
She's going to lunch right now.
She's going to lunch.
Whoever comes closest wins.
You can decide who wins.
Well, that's not going to change.
I'll see you in the comments.
You're right.
She was really good at this.
Let's do that.
The second one is Kira's first one.
That's the second one.
So we're finally going to do this?
Let's do it backwards.
Okay.
How far do you want to go?
To the flake.
What?What?
Okay, okay, okay.
This is as close as we're gonna get.
I'm going to be Kira.
Like this.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Just be Yuzuha's Kira.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Queen.
Oh, you're not moving.
We have to stay in the center.
It's closed all the way.
The corners are good.
Oh, no, this is hard.
Okay, all right, I'm on it.
Just use it as my minimum.
Okay? Yes, please.
Here we go.
Oh, wow!
Oh, perfect!
I don't need a quick one.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
That's pretty perfect.
No, thanks.
Now that I've learned it.
Oh, wow.
What?
I got it.
That's great.
You're studying.
I said please.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't understand.I don't know.
I don't know.
Yes, sir.
You totally remember. Twice.
Thank you for watching.
What did you remember?
I didn't remember any of it.
I only remembered the first time.
Only the first time.
Shake it yourself.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is it perfect?
But I'm always diagonally behind you, Kiro.
I'm always behind you.
I'm sure he's watching you.
I didn't think so.
Stop it.
Do it properly.
Please, please, please.
What did you just think was wacking?
Click!
Boo hoo, but I feel like this is the best I can do for the 8th.
Oh, good, because I'm thinking, "Hey, you know what?
Patty, I know what you're doing, but you always say you're afraid you're going to get hit.
I'll do it anytime!
I'll do it anytime I want to!
Blade & on That girl
I don't do that in the song, but...
I'm not doing that in the song, but I'm in an arms race to see who's going to be the lime's blade and on.
with movement?
I'm free to move.
No particular moves?
No movement.
You are allowed to move, right?
I'm singing.I'm singing, though.
I'm not singing.
You're already singing?
You're a little shorter than her.
Or that you're not as pretty as that girl.
If you have a complex...
I don't know if I can do it.
It's amazing.
It's like perspective.
That's what it's about, right?
A championship is a competition.
You're gonna have to get past me.
You're gonna do this by yourself?
I don't want to.
I don't care if I'm a little shorter or prettier than her, or if I have a lot of complexes.
Did you sing? I sang.
Well, Clear's singing. Yes, I did.
I'm going to recreate love.
Reproduce.
You're a little shorter than you should be?
I'm not sure about the lyrics.
Are you okay?
I'm worried about the lyrics.
Okay.
A little shorter, a little prettier, a little less pretty than that girl.
I'm not prettier than that girl... I don't have any complexes... the list goes on and on...
The timing is wrong.
There's no end to the list.
It's difficult.
There's no end to it.
It's okay, it's okay. It's cute.
What do you mean?
You don't see them like this very often.
That's for sure.
I'm serious, I just sang it.
That's good. I did my best.It's okay. I did my best to be serious.
It was nice. It was so cool.
Wait, when?
It's coming up.
What was that?
You're a little short, or you're not as pretty as that girl...
I mean, how many complexes can you name?
I don't want it.
It's hard.
She's cute, she's cute.
That's great. The editing team is terrible.
But it's like this atmosphere of a live performance.
It's difficult because it's not the atmosphere of a live performance.
That's true.
It's too much.
What kind of expressions do the people watching the video have?
I can't watch this video.
It's too embarrassing.
Let's go next time.
There is more.
Holy Magic.
The fourth one is like Holy Magic.
I knew I was a little bit close to the onkee.
He was the closest.
When he said "Merry Christmas" in a whisper.
What's this?
Merry Christmas.
Yes, sir.
That made you swoon, didn't it?
We'll just have to let the viewers decide.
Hey, 8th and 8th fans.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, there are some who say that.
Yes, there are.
Merry Christmas.Merry Christmas.
Can I speak up for a second? Are you okay with that?
Just be yourself, right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Merry Christmas.
I'm definitely gonna have to put the message out.
I'm not going to let them get away with that.
It's like...
That's funny.
I made him do it here.
It's all about color, isn't it?
It's all about individuality.
Yes, sir.
I'll take care of it.
Is it good?
This guy.
All right, what do you think?
Wrong timing.
Wrong again.
Is his head on?
That was fast.
I didn't see that coming.
Any personality?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like a real Santa Claus.
Like a real Santa Claus inside a real Santa Claus.
Just a little bit.
I got a really good one.
Oh, my God!
I don't want to do this art.
I don't want to do this.
That was good.
Good, good, good.
Okay, let's go south.
Good. South.Oh, thank God. South.
It's all right. It's all right.
You're from Kansai, aren't you?
Maricolai.
Can I go home now?
Can I go now?
I noticed it the most afterwards.
I don't know.
It's good, right? This is...
I think it's good.
Maricolay.
It's difficult.
Maricolle
Live.
I'd like you to do it sometime.
You got this.
Something close to the real thing.
A plan with an arrangement
Which one do you like?
Rust is still there.
Rust.
The last one is...
The one you've all been waiting for
It's not fair!
That's not fair!
What should we do with this?
Let's really make it the last one.
And the dots.
Like before...
It doesn't have to be a story.
Just go for cute and serious.
I'll leave it to you.
Ami, can I go first?
Sure.
I'm off, too.
We're all in the championship as it is.No championship for everyone as it is.
Let's go, Mie!
Mie, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Get in the middle.
Go, go, go, go!
I'm going fast!
Dum-dum-dum!
dun dun dun dun dun dun
It's hard.
That's not fair!
I did it!
Zero was there.
That's not fair!
I think it's good.
That's not fair.
Flounder, right?
Hi, I'm Hirami.
It's a football.
Hi, I'm Minami Hisa.
You're wearing it.
Wow.
I'm cute.
Cute! Cute!
I'm Minami.
Hisa Minami.
That's not fair!
ah ah ah ah, even if you're down in the dumps, you can still press the newest button
Ebinyan, you're all here!
Rim-chan, that's great!
Mirami, you can go south, but you'll have to speak a little higher.
I'm not looking at the page.
I'm not like that... with Queen... when we rehearse... it's so embarrassing...
I'll do it right, I'll do it right, I'll go there and do it.
Speaking of Mirami Ishida, I'm looking forward to it.
That's not fair!That's not fair.
It's like, uh...
I don't want to see your face that bad.
But we were all supposed to turn in together originally.
That's right. What kind of guy is he?
He was originally supposed to rotate us through the Mai performance.
I'd like to see it, though.
I'm going to leave this one up to Minami.
But we did a lot of things, though.
I wonder how it went.
I can't help but worry.
I wonder if everyone will recoil.
Yuu and the others... Yuu's mental health is pretty bad right now.
How are you doing? Embarrassment mentality.
It's pretty bad.
I want to go home.
It's like my body's already puckered up.
It took a lot of courage.
It's been fun.
It's a bit of a mental challenge for me.
I don't know if I'll ever do it again.
It's embarrassing.
It was an interesting project.
In the championship for the prettiest girl in the video
First place went to Kodoko!
What's Kodoko?
This was the song.
Please try to write a lot!
So, thank you very much for watching!
Thank you very much!
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel, give us a high rating, and leave lots of comments!
Please do!
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing D-Holic's costume!
Thank you for watching!Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!